UNITE Vice President's Office Susan Cowell Files 6000/023
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UNITE Vice President's Office Susan Cowell Files
1995-2004
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE)
Cowell, Susan
6000/023
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records.
This collection include some ILGWU materials.
6766592
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, June 19, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 17, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6000 AV: UNITE Audio-Visual Collection 6000 G: UNITE Posters 6000 MB: UNITE Memorabilia 6000 P: UNITE Photographs
Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- New York (State); Clothing trade -- New York (State); Cowell, Susan; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union --Archives; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees; UNITE HERE (Organization) --Archives
6766592
- Hilary Clinton, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Sept 11, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Convention Planning, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Conv. Sta"H"ing, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Conv. Budget, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Convention Logistics, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Booths, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Convention Speakers, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Workshops, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Convention Surveys 2003 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Delegated/Credentials, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Publications, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Officer Elections Campaign, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Officer Elections, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Retiree Program, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Convention: Other Zunites, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Translation 4/2/02, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Choir/Music 4/24/03 - 7/10/03, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  Scope and Contents
  2 Photographs
- Convention Program, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Committees/Resolutions, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- UNITE! Second Constitutional Convention: Proposed Resolutions Assigned to Committees July 2003 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- UNITE! Second Constitutional Convention Composite Resolutions July 2003 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Staging, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Nomination and Election Process July 2003 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Daily Convention Reports July 21-24, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Constitutional Changes July 24-25 2003 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Unaudited Financial Statement July 11, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Misc. Convention Docs. Jul 2003 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Campaign for Growth, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- 2003 Convention Site (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Floor Operations, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- International Program, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Convention Follow-Up, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Convention Procedures, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Committee Resolutions July-Nov 1999 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- '99 Convention Logistics, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Silver Solidarity, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Fighting Sweatshops, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Caucus July 1999 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Finance Ct, 1997-1999 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- 99 Convention, 1999-2002 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Merger Advertising, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- UNITE! Launches National Ad. Campaign Jan 29 1996 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Ad Production, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Advertising - Other Proposals, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Post Convention 95, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Mission Statement 95, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- PR 95, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 48)